(function() {
  
  window.categories = [
    {
      name: 'April Fools!',
      badge: 'Prankster',
      badgeScore: 2,
      quizzes: [
        {
          type: 'fill-blank', 
          question: 'Can you name the Google product from a 2006 April Fools day prank?',
          start: 'Love is just another search problem. Solve it with Google',
          end: '.',
          answer: 'Romance'
        },
        {
          type: 'multi-select',
          question: 'Which of the following April Fools jokes has Google actually done?',
          options: [
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs'
          ],
          answer: '0,1,2'
        },
        {
          type: 'single-select',
          question: 'Which real Google product launched on April Fools Day in 2004?',
          options: [
            'Drive',
            'Calendar',
            'Gmail',
            'Chrome'
          ],
          answer: 2
        },
        {
          type: 'fill-blank', 
          question: 'Can you name the Google product from a 2006 April Fools day prank?',
          start: 'Love is just another search problem. Solve it with Google',
          end: '.',
          answer: 'Romance'
        },
        {
          type: 'multi-select',
          question: 'Which of the following April Fools jokes has Google actually done?',
          options: [
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs'
          ],
          answer: '0,1,2'
        },
        {
          type: 'single-select',
          question: 'Which real Google product launched on April Fools Day in 2004?',
          options: [
            'Drive',
            'Calendar',
            'Gmail',
            'Chrome'
          ],
          answer: 2
        },
        {
          type: 'fill-blank', 
          question: 'Can you name the Google product from a 2006 April Fools day prank?',
          start: 'Love is just another search problem. Solve it with Google',
          end: '.',
          answer: 'Romance'
        },
        {
          type: 'multi-select',
          question: 'Which of the following April Fools jokes has Google actually done?',
          options: [
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs'
          ],
          answer: '0,1,2'
        },
        {
          type: 'single-select',
          question: 'Which real Google product launched on April Fools Day in 2004?',
          options: [
            'Drive',
            'Calendar',
            'Gmail',
            'Chrome'
          ],
          answer: 2
        },
        {
          type: 'fill-blank', 
          question: 'Can you name the Google product from a 2006 April Fools day prank?',
          start: 'Love is just another search problem. Solve it with Google',
          end: '.',
          answer: 'Romance'
        },
        {
          type: 'multi-select',
          question: 'Which of the following April Fools jokes has Google actually done?',
          options: [
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs'
          ],
          answer: '0,1,2'
        },
        {
          type: 'single-select',
          question: 'Which real Google product launched on April Fools Day in 2004?',
          options: [
            'Drive',
            'Calendar',
            'Gmail',
            'Chrome'
          ],
          answer: 2
        },
        {
          type: 'fill-blank', 
          question: 'Can you name the Google product from a 2006 April Fools day prank?',
          start: 'Love is just another search problem. Solve it with Google',
          end: '.',
          answer: 'Romance'
        },
        {
          type: 'multi-select',
          question: 'Which of the following April Fools jokes has Google actually done?',
          options: [
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs'
          ],
          answer: '0,1,2'
        },
        {
          type: 'single-select',
          question: 'Which real Google product launched on April Fools Day in 2004?',
          options: [
            'Drive',
            'Calendar',
            'Gmail',
            'Chrome'
          ],
          answer: 2
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      name: 'I/O Trivia', 
      badge: 'I/O Expert',
      badgeScore: 1,
      quizzes: [
        {
          type: 'single-select', 
          question: 'When was the first Google I/O?',
          options: [
            '2006',
            '2007',
            '2008',
            '2014'
          ],
          answer: 2
        },
        {
          type: 'multi-select',
          question: 'What are the 3 I/O themes this year?',
          options: [
            'Doodle',
            'Design',
            'Debug',
            'Develop',
            'Distribute',
            'Decode'
          ],
          answer: '1,3,4'
        }
      ]
    }
  ];
  
})();